AZIZBEK MUXTORQULOV

FRONTEND DEVELOPER

DETAILS

ADDRESS

Tashkent Uzbekistan

PHONE

909969811

EMAIL

muxtorqulovaziz@gmail.com

LINKS

My portfolio website

<u>Telegram</u>

<u>Github</u>

You tube

SKILLS

HTML

• • • • •

CSS

• • • •

React

• • • •

Git

• • • •

JavaScript

• • • • •

TypeScript

● ● ● O O

Tailwind Css

 \bullet \bullet \circ \circ

Wordpress

• • • • •

HOBBIES

Playing Chess, Learning new skills, interAl

LANGUAGES

PROFILE

Highly skilled and experienced Frontend Developer with over 1 years of experience designing and implementing user-friendly and responsive web applications. Strong proficiency in HTML, CSS, JavaScript, and various frontend frameworks. Passionate about creating visually appealing and engaging websites and applications that provide an exceptional user experience.

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Web teacher, IT park

Sirdaryo

Nov 2021 — Jan 2023

· Worked with web staff to develop more invigorating web content.

Web devoloper, IT park

Sirdaryo

Apr 2022 — Jan 2023

- · Developed and implemented user interfaces for various clients' websites
- Utilized ReactJS and other frontend frameworks to create responsive and user-friendly websites
- \cdot $\,$ Ensured cross-browser compatibility and accessibility
- · Collaborated with designers to create visually appealing designs
- Conducted code reviews and implemented continuous improvement strategies

Web devoloper, in the state of the city

Shirin

Jan 2023 — Apr 2023

- Collaborate with designers and developers to create responsive and visually appealing web applications
- · Develop and maintain the company's website using ReactJS
- · Implement user interfaces using HTML, CSS, and JavaScript
- · Conduct code reviews to ensure code quality and adherence to best practices

EDUCATION

under Gulistan state University, Secondary Education, Yangiyer Academic Lyceum

Yangiyer

Sep 2014 — May 2017

Achived: I participated in the regional Olympiad

Bachelor, Tashkent State Technical University

Tashkent

Sep 2017 — May 2021

engineer

Frontend dev, Red fox IT academy

Tashkent

Jun 2021

Uzbek

 \bullet

Russian

 \bullet \bullet \circ \circ

English

 \bullet \bullet \circ \circ

state project, one million devoloper

Uzbekistan

Apr 2021

COURSES

Web , Udemy

Apr 2022 — Jan 2023

English for IT, Mohirdev

Jan 2022 — Jan 2023

IELTS, Personal teacher

Mar 2023

React js, Mohirdev

Jan 2022 — Nov 2022

EXTRA-CURRICULAR ACTIVITIES